# **Trevor Clare**

Tarzana, CA TrevorClare.ccna@gmail.com 8053022545

Professional Network and Systems Engineer with 3+ years of experience in all areas at the Enterprise level involving Networking and Systems Security, including design and maintaining complex systems to improve the availability of all Enterprise technology assets.

#### **CORE STRENGTHS**

OSI Model, TCP\IP Model, Routing & Switching, Firewall Configuration, LAN Technologies, Wireless Technologies, Network Analysis, Network Architecture, Network Administration, Network Management, Network Monitoring: Kibana, Cacti, Scrutinizer, PRTG, Grafana, Sonar, RRD, SMC, Network Security, Network Diagramming, Server Virtualization, Active Directory, Group Policy, DHCP, O365, GSUITE, AZURE, AWS, DHCP, DNS, Project management, Windows Server, Linux, Scripting, Remote Monitoring Management, HVAC, Team Player, Cross-Functional

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

## **Network Support Engineer**

Sohonet Inc. - Los Angeles, CA March 2021 to Present

Sohonet is a community-of-interest network for the television, film, and media production community. Founded by a group of post-production companies based in the Soho area of London, Sohonet links many British film studios to London's post-production community.

- · Installing and configuring network equipment such as firewalls, routers, and switches
- Performing ongoing monitoring and troubleshooting to find innovative ways to improve network performance
- Conducting regular maintenance tasks such as scheduling updates, performing network upgrades, managing security configurations, and installing patches and or service packs
- Collaborating and or communicating with third-party support services and service providers to ensure network functionality and optimization
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills
- · Highly adaptable to any information technology environment, whether current, changing, or unfamiliar
- Technical liaison and or consultant for varying clients within the media entertainment industry with a direct emphasis on building customer relationships to provide white-glove technology services

### **Network and Systems Administrator**

Columbia College Hollywood January 2020 to March 2021

Columbia College Hollywood is a non-profit liberal arts college with degree programs in Cinema, Visual Effects, Graphic Design, and Interactive Media.

- Maintenance and administration of all computer networks
- · Oversight and management of all installed information systems and infrastructure
- The setting, implementing, testing, and maintenance of all operating systems, application software, and system management tools
- System evaluation and technical direction to technical support staff
- Oversight, and management, of customized cloud application software
- Monitoring of system resource availability
- Timely reporting and tracking of all incidents for rapid response to any system failure

## **NOC Engineer**

Multacom Corporation June 2019 to January 2020

Multacom Inc. is an award-winning data center provider delivering custom dedicated servers, dedicated hosting, and colocation solutions.

- Documentation and reporting of all new accounts
- Power failure monitoring on all data center network and server systems
- Vendor ticket management
- Monitoring and rapid incident response on data center threats like DDoS attacks
- Hardware configuration including customer security appliances and data center L3 distribution layer switches
- Network analysis and routine troubleshooting
- Support, configuration, maintenance, and upgrading of all networks and infrastructures for corporations
- · Diagramming of network cabling, network classification, and network topology
- Administration, customer care, and support on all Linux or Windows Server deployments

### **Internship - Network Engineer**

Amgen

November 2016 to November 2017

Amgen is one of the world's leading biotechnology companies. Amgen is a values-based company deeply rooted in science and innovation to transform new ideas and discoveries into medicines for patients with serious illnesses.

- Performed network systems engineering including performance analysis, maintainability analysis, capacity analysis, and reliability analysis
- Forecasted network needs and worked with other information systems team to develop policies and procedures

#### **Internship - Architect Support**

Amgen

June 2015 to August 2015

Diagramming and documentation of all Amgen MPLS networks, including circuit removal, upgrades, or install

• Team Collaboration and end-user engagement to discover and resolve issues in Amgen's NextGen workspace

• Infrastructure planning and vetting of emerging technologies to improve Amgen's global enterprise service delivery

### Education

# **Bachelor of Applied Science in Network Operations**

University of Arizona

March 2017 to 2021

# Certifications and Licenses

# **Cisco Certified Entry Networking Technician (CCENT)**

**CCNA Udemy** 

**CompTIA Security+ Udemy** 

**CCNA Expected July 2021 (Pending)** 

# University of Arizona - Expected Completion in 2021

GPA: 4.0

Dean's List 2021

#### Relevant Courses:

CYBV 301 - Fundamentals of Cybersecurity

CYBV 326 - Intro Methods of Network Analysis

CYBV 329 - Cyber Ethics

INFV 379 - Cloud Computing

NFV 370 - Intro to Network Design & Architecture

NETV 374 - Routing Theories+Application

NETV 375 - Advanced Routing+Wan Technologies

APCV 320 - Computational Thinking & Doing (Python Programming)